searchall.com 2019-04-09

# SearchAll

### SearchAll.com Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

Elevated Media Inc respects your privacy and we are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This policy governs all websites, apps, and other services that link to, or contain references to, this document and are published or made available by Elevated Media Inc and/or its affiliates (“we”, “our” or “us”).

Our services include our websites and applications that link to this privacy policy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you use our services and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * When you use or interact with our services.
  * In your email, text, and other electronic messages with us.
  * Through our mobile and desktop applications.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our services. By accessing or using our services, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to Our Privacy Policy). Your continued use of our services after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

## EU-US Privacy Shield and Swiss-US Privacy Shield

Elevated Media Inc complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Elevated Media Inc has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.

To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

Elevated Media Inc is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC).

## Children Under the Age of 13

Our services are not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or through our services. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information through our services. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at:

Email – info@elevatedmediainc.com  
Full Address – Click Here

## Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

We collect some statistical data from and about users of our services, including information:

  * that is about you but individually does not identify you, such as your IP address, referral data, and browser and platform type

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you use our services. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies.
  * From third parties, for example, our business partners.

## Information You Provide to Us

The information we collect through our services may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms through our services. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our services, subscribing to our service, posting material, or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our services.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.

## Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies

As you use our services, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

  * Details of your use of our services, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you use on our services.
  * Information about your internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include personal information.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our services. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our services.
  * Flash Cookies. Certain features of our services may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our services. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies.
  * Web Beacons. Portions of our services may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that allow us, for example, to count users who have visited pages and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

We do not collect personal information.

## How We Use Your Statistical Data

We use statistical data that we collect about you or that you provide to us,

  * To present our services and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To provide you with notices about your account, including expiration and renewal notices.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  * To notify you about changes to our services.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our services.
  * In any other way, we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

## Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which your information held by us is among the assets transferred.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose the information we collect:

  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect our rights, property, or for our safety, and that of our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  * Under certain circumstances, we may be required to disclose your information in response to valid requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
  * Elevated Media Inc’s accountability for data it receives pursuant to the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield and subsequent transfer of that data to third parties is detailed in the Privacy Shield Principles. In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of EU or Swiss individuals received pursuant to the EU-US or and Swiss-US Privacy Shield, Elevated Media Inc is potentially liable. In particular, Elevated Media Inc remains responsible and liable under the Privacy Shield Principles if third-party agents that it engages to process the data on its behalf do so in a manner inconsistent with the Principles unless Elevated Media Inc proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

## Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
  * For some of our products, we use Google Analytics Advertising Features. For information about Google Analytics currently available opt-outs, please click [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).
  * Some of our products may include advertisements from Microsoft. To learn more about information collected by Microsoft, please click [here](http://www.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement/Default.aspx). You can opt-out of Microsoft’s personalized advertising services by following the instructions found [here](http://choice.microsoft.com/).
  * We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However, these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can also generally opt-out of receiving personalized ads from third party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the [Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) or who follow the [Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI site and DAA site.
  * Elevated Media Inc acknowledges that EU and Swiss individuals have the right to access the data that we maintain about them. An EU or Swiss individual(s) who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data, should direct their query to Elevated Media Inc. If requested to remove data, we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.
  * We will also provide an EU or Swiss individual(s) with opt-out or opt-in choice before we share their data with third parties other than our agents, or before we use it for a purpose other than which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized.
  * To limit the use and disclosure of your information, please submit a written request to: Email – info@elevatedmediainc.com | Full Address – Click Here

## Data Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your statistical data information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your information, we cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted to our services. Any transmission of information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the services.

## Dispute Resolutions

In compliance with the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles, Elevated Media Inc commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Elevated Media Inc.

Elevated Media Inc has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit <http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers> for more information and to file a complaint.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint>, you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolutions procedures have been exhausted.

## Changes To Our Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will let you know through a notice in our services. The date the privacy policy was last revised is found at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting this privacy policy to check for any changes.

## Contact Information

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:

Email – info@elevatedmediainc.com  
Full Address – Click Here

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS CONTAINED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY EXIT THE SERVICE.

Last modified: May 24, 2018
